

Applicant for:

Al Engineer (Machine Learning, Python)

TMA Solutions 7 June 2019

Huy Ngo

□ ngodotronghuy@gmail.com

Main interests: Python, Java

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Huy Ngo skipped the cover letter.



179 Khuong Viet, Tan Phu Dist, TPHCM

huyngo0690@gmail.com

0909162948

12/09/1993

SUMMARY

I have one year experience as Java developer at Smart OSC company and six months in Quodisys. At Quodisys, I learnt a lot via projects, adapt new technology like VueJs and NodeJS, working with python(Django). I also have knowledge about database, I worked with Oracle Database for 4 months when I were an intern at Hoa Binh Corp.

SKILLS

Python

SQL

Java

JavaScript ••••

Machine Learning Algorithms

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate

INTERESTS

Ngo Do Trong Huy

Developer

EXPERIENCES

Internship

Hoa Binh Corporation | 12/2016 - 04/2017

Working with Oracle Database: install, create database, select query.

Using Oracle forms and reports to create forms for IT department manage equipments and reports at weekend.

Junior Java Developer

SmartOSC

08/2017 - 07/2018

Using Java core, apache camel components(http4), Spring boot, APIs

Using AEM CMS from adobe to create components and templates.

Backend Developer

Quodisys

| 10/2018 - Present

Javascript, VueJS, PHP, HTML, CSS, Python.

Developing Lasso plugin in WordPress as a UI for client, using AWS as a server to build update server, maintain version of plugin.

PROJECTS

- Unicorn: E-comerce website, using AEM and Spring 4 members Main role:
 Create components and edit template
- Pham Nguyen Food: E-comerce website using magento integration with Spring -Main role: using java parsing JSON, reading info from pdf file.
- Lasso plugin: Wordpress plugin Main role: Working in backend, logic function, update UI. Apply Vue JS for FE, assign value to Vue object in each input field in HTML, get value from PHP function using AJAX.
- Compliy(Web-App) Main role: Logic and backend, using Django for login, register function. Move functions from Django to NodeJS.

EDUCATION

Computer Network

Hoa Sen University-College degree | 10/2011 - 2014

Information System

Centria University-Bachelor degree | 08/2015 - 12/2017

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Have soft skills, friendly, fun with colleagues.

Good self-study, team work or work individual